(Penny:)Hey, have you ever heard of
the Van Nuys Comic-Con?
‭Yeah.
(Leonard:)It's a dinky little convention
where they sell collectibles
(Leonard:)and get sad D-list celebrities
to appear. Why?
(Penny:)I got asked
to sign autographs there.
That's awesome!
(Leonard:)Is this for
Serial Ape-ist?
(Penny:)Well, it could be
for the monkey movie.
(Penny:)It could be
my hemorrhoid commercial.
(Penny:)The list does not go on.
- When is it?
- It doesn't matter.
(Penny:)I'm not doing it.
(Leonard:)What? Why not?
(Penny:)You just said yourself,
it's sad.
(Leonard:)Yeah, but it's
not pathetic.
(Leonard:)That's where
I draw the line.
Come on! We'll have fun.
(Penny:)I don't know.
(Leonard:)You'll have nerds
fawning all over you.
(Leonard:)If you don't love that,
this marriage is in trouble.
(Penny:)I guess it wouldn't hurt
to meet some fans
(Penny:)and make a little extra money.
(Leonard:)Yeah.
Wow! An appearance
by George Lucas...
...'s dermatologist.
(Leonard:)- Oh, I want that autograph.
- Oh, yeah.